(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Dream Festival -Nakiri Ayame 7th Birthday-
Welcome to the Birthday Live!
百鬼あやめ
Nakiri Ayame
COUNTDOWN START
はずむココロ　飛んじゃうテンション！　さあ Connect しよ！
Pounding heart, soaring tension! Let's connect!
I mean… No More Hiding Now.
Changing… So I’m Trying Now.
あれ？　いま 曇ってて、あ、じゃなくって…
Huh? It's cloudy now... no, that's not it...
えっと あの、 なんて言うんだっけ？
Um, what's that thing you say?
どうするんだっけ…　ああ、 ああ…
What was I supposed to do... ah, ah...
しっちゃかめっちゃか Thinking　ぐるぐる Now Loading...
Helter-skelter thinking, spinning now loading...
[Ctrl]+[Z] もきかないし
Even [Ctrl]+[Z] doesn't work
複雑カスタマイズ　足りない？ 何か
Complex customization, is something missing?
インストール とかできたらな
If only I could just install it
なんて不完全で。 正解は何だって。
How incomplete. What is the right answer?
なんて不確定で。 答えはどこだって。
How uncertain. Where is the answer?
説明書なんてないよね　まずは
There's no instruction manual, is there? First,
始めてみようかな…
I think I'll just start...
違う姿
Different figures,
違うカタチ
different shapes,
なのにどうして
yet why the
同じ気持ち
same feelings?
繋がってる実感
The feeling of being connected,
分け合う温もり
the warmth we share,
ありがとう
thank you.
思いっきり伝えたいんだ！
I want to tell you with all my heart!
カラフル笑顔
Your colorful smiles
心地いいな
feel so good.
繋がっていくみんなと
Connecting with everyone,
ここが私の好きな場所
this is the place I love.
はずむココロ　飛んじゃうテンション！　今 Connect しよ！
Pounding heart, soaring tension! Let's connect now!
I mean… No More Hiding Now.
Changing… So I’m Trying Now.
きっと頑張ってみたって　変われないって　諦めて
Thinking that no matter how hard I try, I won't change, giving up.
トライしてみる手前で　断念して　あわわわ
Giving up right before even trying, awawawa.
部屋でぼっち Crying
Crying alone in my room,
ネガティブばっか My mind
my mind full of negatives,
思ったようにいかなくて
things not going as planned.
ポッキリ折れてた
I want to make my heart,
心も一度
which was snapped in two,
踊らせていきたいんだ
dance once more.
いいよ不完全で。
It's okay to be incomplete.
いっそ言っちゃえ。
Just say it.
もう隠さないんだ。
I won't hide anymore.
表情は一つじゃない
There's more than one expression.
理想へ届かなくても
Even if I don't reach my ideal,
一歩
one step...
踏み出してみようかな…
I think I'll try taking a step...
違う色と
With different colors
違う夢で
and different dreams,
進むミライ
the future ahead
きっとステキ
will surely be wonderful.
見えないけど感じる
I can't see it but I feel it,
君に私にできること
What you and I can do
見つけていくから
I'll keep finding them
Ah...
うーん
Uun
違う形　違う形なのに　ホントだ　同じ気持ち
Different shapes, even though we're in different shapes, it's true, we feel the same way
繋がってる　今
Connected now
分け合う温もり　ありがとう
Sharing the warmth, thank you
思いっきり伝えたいんだ！
I want to tell you with all my heart!
カラフル！笑顔　心地いいね
Colorful! Smiling faces, it feels so good
繋がってく　みんなと
Connecting with everyone
ここが私の好きな場所
This is my favorite place
弾むココロ！　飛び出すセッション
A bouncing heart! A session that jumps out
To Connect しよ！
Let's connect!
I mean... No more hiding now
Changing... So I'm trying now
百鬼あやめ生誕祭2024
Dream Festival!! Nakiri Ayame 7th BirthDay
Nakiri Ayame Birthday Festival 2024
Dream Festival!! Nakiri Ayame 7th Birthday
踊れオーケストラ
作詞・作曲：YASUHIRO(康寛)
Odore Orchestra
Lyrics/Composition: YASUHIRO
さあさあこの指に止まれ
Come, come, land on this finger
後悔あとで知っても知らないぞ
I won't care even if you regret it later
音に呑まれて
Swallowed by the sound
歌って踊って満たすだけ
Just sing and dance to fill yourself up
パパパン　手を打ち鳴らして
Clap-clap-clap, clap your hands
そうそう　足取りも軽快に
Yes, yes, with a light step
音色を足して
Add more tones
今導き出すよ
I'll guide you now
正体は実は案外
The true identity is actually quite
歯がゆいもの
frustrating
魔法のタクト、空にかざすだけ
Just hold the magic baton up to the sky
おいでよ　街を包み込んだ超常現象が
Come on, a supernatural phenomenon that has wrapped up the town
夜空にほら響き渡って　退屈が泣きだす
Look, it echoes through the night sky, and boredom starts to cry
孤独な愛を産めよ　最終楽章アンサンブルを
Give birth to lonely love, an ensemble of the final movement
君は聞こえた？
Did you hear it?
星に舞う旋律を
The melody dancing in the stars
ワン・ツー・スリー・シで鳴いてた
One, two, three, four, I was crying
過去に負けない巡る力を
A rotating power that won't lose to the past
タンタン　楽しいリズムで
Clap clap, with a fun rhythm
途切れない音を乗せて
Carrying an unending sound
愛を奏でよう　この空に
Let's play love in this sky
忘れてた景色の向こうの　その向こう
Beyond the landscape I'd forgotten, and beyond that
未定調和のほころび
A rift in the undetermined harmony
モノクロの望遠鏡
A monochrome telescope
待ったはなしのぶっつけ本番で
No waiting, just jump right into the performance
奏でよう　理想輝く幻想的進行で
Let's play with a fantastical progression where ideals shine
いつも目が合うあいつと　手を繋ぎ踊ろう
Let's hold hands and dance with that person our eyes always meet with
何度も　泣いて泣いた心の悲歌（エレジー）を
The elegy of the heart that has cried and cried many times
僕は聞こえた、
I heard it,
だから今ここにいるんだ
That's why I'm here now
正体は実は案外
The true identity is actually quite
悲しいもの
sad
魔法の音色、空に響かせて
Let the magic tones echo through the sky
おいでよ　街を包み込んだ超常現象が
Come on, a supernatural phenomenon that has wrapped up the town
夜空にほら響き渡って　退屈が泣きだす
Look, it echoes through the night sky, and boredom starts to cry
愉快な歌を歌おう　最終演奏アンサンブルを
Let's sing a cheerful song, an ensemble of the final performance
君は聞こえた？
Did you hear it?
星に舞う旋律を
The melody dancing in the stars
ワン・ツー・スリー・シで鳴いてた過去に負けない巡る力を
One, two, three, four, a rotating power that won't lose to the past I was crying in
繋ぐ力を
The power to connect
たったた楽しいリズムで
With a fun, fun rhythm
途切れない音をのせて さあさ
Carrying the unending sound, come now
パンパン手を打ち鳴らして
Clap, clap your hands
踊れ踊れ オーケストラ
Dance, dance, orchestra
バイバイ今夜はサヨナラ
Bye-bye, tonight is goodbye
次は君もステージで
Next time you'll be on stage too
さあさこの指にとまれ
Come on, join in with me
後悔後でしてもしらないぞ
I won't care if you regret it later
耳をすまして
Listen closely
僕らと踊るだけ
Just dance with us
これでいいのだ
This is fine
ハオ ハオ ハオ
Hao, hao, hao
好きの需要と供給の寒暖差
The temperature gap between demand and supply of love
また風邪っぴきさん
Another person with a cold
忍法修行は効率が肝心だ
Efficiency is key in ninja training
とかわかってるもん
I know all that
でも簡単じゃない
But it's not easy
ねえ 簡単じゃないの
Hey, it's not easy
心の乙女が
The maiden in my heart
あれこれ言っちゃうの
Says this and that
問題が大
It's a big problem
ねえ 頑張ってドクター
Hey, do your best, doctor
感情が爆散
Emotions are exploding
頭あちちな
My head is burning up
ハオ ハオ ハオ のラブ連単
Hao hao hao's love trifecta
君としたいことがいっぱい
So many things I want to do with you
「いつも足んないな」
"It's never enough"
ってなる問題
That's the problem
欲張り星人のせいなんだ
It's because I'm a greedy alien
うー もう嫌い嫌い嫌い嫌い
Ugh, I hate you, hate you, hate you, hate you
大嫌いとか思ってみたい
I want to try thinking I hate you
でも ハオ ハオ ハオ のラブ連単
But, Hao hao hao's love trifecta
“愛したほうが勝ち”なんだって
"The one who loves is the winner," they say
これでいいのだ ハオ ハオ
This is fine, hao hao
ところがどっこい
Wait a minute
脳がお目覚めだ
My brain is waking up
バッドだらけのぱーりない
Party night full of bad things
もうダメだ
It's no good anymore
誰にでも嫉妬しちゃって
Getting jealous of anyone
胸が取れそう
My heart's about to fall out
最高セット こっち向いて
Best set, look this way
最低セット あっち向いて
Worst set, look away
感情は日替わり
Emotions change daily
ヘイ テンションチャンプルー
Hey, tension champuru
また押すっきゃない
Got no choice but to push it again
ねえ 押すっきゃないの
Hey, I've got no choice
あたしが重すぎて
I'm too heavy
揺れない恋心
Unwavering love
問題が大
It's a big problem
ねえ 頑張ってドクター
Hey, do your best, doctor
残念が爆散
Regret is exploding
頭あちちな
My head is burning up
ハオ ハオ ハオ のラブ連単
Hao hao hao's love trifecta
気持ちを抑え込んで一旦
Holding back my feelings for now
「きみが足んないな」
"You're not enough"
ってなるような
Like that
大人バランスがいいんだって
An adult balance is better, they say
忙しいだなんてうそ
It's a lie that I'm busy
ごめん寝てたなんてうそ
It's a lie that I was sleeping
迷走しちゃう あたし
I'm losing my way
安らかに死ねばいいのに
I wish I could just die peacefully
ハオ ハオ ハオ のラブ連単
Hao hao hao's love trifecta
これでいいのかな
Is this okay?
頭あちちな
My head is burning up
ハオ ハオ ハオ のラブ連単
Hao hao hao's love trifecta
きみのしたいことも頂戴
Tell me what you want to do too
刺激バッキュンビーム 打ち放題
Unlimited shots of stimulating beam
欲張り星人になっちゃいな
Become a greedy alien
うー 大嫌い嫌い嫌い嫌い
Ugh, I hate you, hate you, hate you, hate you
超嫌いとか思っちゃうの？
You think you super hate me?
やだ ハオ ハオ ハオ のラブ連単
No, Hao hao hao's love trifecta
愛されちゃうのを欲しがっています
Longing to be loved
へっちゃらピーポー
Carefree people
イタさも逆にオッケー
Cringey is okay too
はっちゃけピーポー
Letting loose people
ダサさも逆にオッケー
Uncool is okay too
ぶっちゃけピーポー
Frankly speaking people
ウザさも逆にオッケー
Annoying is okay too
言ったらいいじゃん
Just say it
せーので ハオ ハオ
One, two, Hao hao
へっちゃらピーポー イタさも逆にオッケー
Carefree people, cringey is okay too
はっちゃけピーポー ダサさも逆にオッケー
Letting loose people, uncool is okay too
ぶっちゃけピーポー ウザさも逆にオッケー
Frankly speaking people, annoying is okay too
言ったらいいじゃん せーので ハオ ハオ
Just say it, one, two, Hao hao
これでいいのだ ハオ ハオ
This is fine, hao hao
はい、皆さーん！
Yes, everyone!
百鬼あやめ生誕祭2024にお越しくださりありがとうございます！
Thank you for coming to Nakiri Ayame Birthday Celebration 2024!
やっぞー！
Yazzo!
改めまして、ホロライブ2期生の百鬼あやめです！
Once again, I'm Nakiri Ayame from Hololive's 2nd Generation!
ありがとー、皆来てくれてありがとうねー！
Thank you, thank you all for coming!
えー、今回の配信なんですけど
Um, about today's stream...
右上にありますこちら！
This one right here in the top right!
ハッシュタグ #百鬼あやめ生誕祭2024 で
With the hashtag #NakiriAyameBirthday2024...
あの、スクショやら、感想やらをぜひたくさんポストしてくれると余が嬉しいです！
I'd be very happy if you'd post lots of screenshots and impressions!
ぜひぜひ、シュシュシュッとポストしてくださいね、皆さん。よろしくお願いします。
Please, please, post them quickly, everyone. Thank you in advance.
ということでですね、皆さん、ちょっとお気づきになられましたでしょうか？
And so, everyone, did you happen to notice?
ここまでの繋がるコネクト、「踊れオーケストラ」、「ハオ」
The "Connect" linking up to now—"Odore Orchestra", "Hao"...
この曲やってる中で皆さん、
While performing these songs, everyone...
うんこ！
Poop!
あれ、うんこ？
Wait, poop?
今まで見たことない、うんこ演出しちゃったなーみたいな、お気づきになられましたよね？
A poop production like I've never seen before... you noticed, right?
あ、はいはい。あ、そうですそうです。
Ah, yes yes. Oh, right right.
こちらです！このね、階段演出、今回初めてやらせていただきました。
It's this! These stairs, I got to use them for the first time.
皆気づいたかな？このね、
Did everyone notice? This...
でっかいこの、このパネルから、あの、ゲストの皆さんやら余がこう降りてきて、
From this huge panel, the guests and I come down like this...
こう、こんな、ええ～っはあ～みたいな感じを、やらせていただいたんですけど
I was just doing this kind of "Whoa, wow!" reaction...
でもすごいでしょう、このね扉も開くんですよ。この...
But isn't it amazing? This door even opens. This...
おお！開いた、開いた！ここ、ここ。これこれこれ。ありがとうございます。
Oh! It opened, it opened! Right here. This is it. Thank you so much.
このね、あの光ってるところから皆が出てくるんですけれども。
This glowing part is where everyone will be coming out from.
そしてねちょっと、ステージの紹介もさせていただこうかなと思うんですけど、
I'd also like to take a moment to introduce the stage, but...
ちょっと開けっぱなしになっちゃった。ちょっと閉めるか。
Oh, I left it open. Let me close it real quick.
ういっ！
Hup!
あ、ちょっと、ちょっと！はい。
Ah, wait, wait! There.
ということでですね、今回ライブのねステージ、ちょっとすごいいろんな方が来てくれてます。見て！
So, for today's live stage, we have all sorts of guests here. Look!
まずはこちらのね、動物たちをちょっと見ていただこうかな。見えるかな？
First, let's take a look at these animals. Can you see them?
ああ～ね！可愛いでしょ。猫ちゃんやらね、あのクマさんやら、あのたくさんウサギちゃんやらね。
Aren't they cute? There are cats, bears, and lots of bunnies.
こうたくさん動物が、このステージで踊ってくれてます。そして！
So many animals are dancing here on stage. And!
皆気づいたかな。このぽよよもね、見て！
Did you all notice? Look at the Poyoyo too!
今回のライブのコンセプトの仕様に合わせて、ぽよよもね、楽器を持ってくれてたり、
To match the concept of this live concert, the Poyoyo are holding instruments,
あとお帽子をね、お帽子被ってくれてます。かわいい～！
and they're even wearing little hats. So cute!
はい！ということで、今回のライブのステージはですね。コンセプトは、
Alright! So, for the stage of this live concert...
えー皆ね、こう夢のような楽しい時間を過ごしてほしいなということで、
the concept is that I want everyone to have a dream-like, fun time.
ちょっとパレードっぽいような、お祭りのようなちょっと賑やかな感じに、可愛く明るい感じにさせていただきました。
We've made it lively, cute, and bright, like a parade or a festival.
ね、今回のライブを通して、皆がね、楽しい気持ちになってくれたら嬉しいなと思っております。
I hope this concert brings a smile to everyone's face.
ね、この先もね、あの、えっ！これこそ歌って踊るの？みたいな、
Moving forward, we'll have guests that might make you go,
初めてね、出てくれるゲストの方やらもいらっしゃいますので、
"Wait, they're going to sing and dance to this?" for the first time!
ぜひこの先も楽しんでいただければなと思います。この先も、見てってねー！
So please keep enjoying the show until the very end!
どうしたら　あなたに愛を　刻めるんだろう
How can I carve my love into you?
DEAREST DROP
作詞・作曲: Q-MHz
Lyrics & Composition: Q-MHz
知らない気持ちばかり覚えたよ　忘れ方も教えて
I've only learned feelings I never knew; please teach me how to forget too.
言葉だけじゃなくてさ　震える指の温度から
Not just through words, but from the warmth of trembling fingers.
それは誰の希望？　私から溢れ出した願いのドロップ
Whose hope is it? A drop of a wish overflowing from within me.
消えても　消えても　生まれてくるけど　答えなき脆い未来
Even if it fades, it's born again and again; a fragile future with no answer.
何回目の明日が来るのか分からない夜なら
In a night where I don't know how many tomorrows will come...
名前を呼ばれたい　ただ胸が痛い痛くて張り裂けそうだよ
I want my name to be called; it just hurts so much, my heart is about to burst.
どうしたら　あなたに愛を　刻めるんだろう
How can I carve my love into you?
私がいつか空に　溶け去る前に
Before I eventually dissolve into the sky.
強い想いで今を　守りたくなった
I've come to want to protect this moment with all my strength.
理由はあなたをもっと　見ていたいから
Because the reason is, I want to keep looking at you.
程良い笑顔なんていらないよ　甘い嘘で隠した
I don't need a polite smile; I've hidden it all with sweet lies.
傷を分かち合えたら　嘆きも飲み込む意味がある
If we can share our wounds, there's a reason to swallow the grief.
そして夢に変われ　あなたへと伝えたい誓いのドロップ
Then let it turn into a dream; a drop of a vow I want to convey to you.
叶わない　叶わない　気づいてるんだけどね　捧げるんだ祈りを
It won't come true, I know that, but I'll still offer up my prayer.
永遠じゃない存在でも　確かな光を欲しがる
Even if we aren't eternal beings, we still yearn for a certain light.
危うい運命だよ　もっと一緒にいてよ　世界が壊れても
It's a perilous fate; stay with me more, even if the world falls apart.
いつだって　心は愛を　止められない
The heart can never stop its love.
あなたはいつも何を　探しているの？
What is it that you're always searching for?
暗い闇へと今を　浮かべてみたけれど
I tried to let the present float into the dark shadows, but...
あなたをそばで
I'll be watching you closely
見つめていよう
from by your side.
もしも 問いかけて 声は 風の中
If I ask a question, my voice in the wind...
小さくなってく
...is fading away.
すべてを 話してよ
Tell me everything.
そっと抱きしめてあげたいよ
I want to hold you gently.
なのに 流れる時間が示すのは
And yet, what the passing time shows...
ずれながら遠ざかる二人
...is the two of us drifting apart.
どうしたら あなたに愛を刻めるの
How can I engrave my love into you?
いつだって心は愛を止められない
My heart can never stop loving.
何を探しているの
What are you looking for?
強い思いで今を守りたくなった
With strong feelings, I wanted to protect the present.
理由は あなたをもっと見ていたくて
The reason is that I wanted to see more of you,
空に溶け去るまでは
until it melts away into the sky.
流れ星空へと打ち返す
I'll hit back shooting stars towards the sky!
ドゥノット、ウォーリー
Do not, worry!
ホームラン かぐや姫が叫ぶ
Home run! Princess Kaguya screams.
9回裏のストーリー
A story from the bottom of the 9th.
驚いたUFOが落ちてく
A surprised UFO is falling down.
やりすぎ！？アイアムソーリー
Did I overdo it!? I'm sorry.
目が覚めてティーチャーが微笑んだ
I woke up and the teacher was smiling.
絶体絶命！？
A desperate situation!?
充電がフルになるまで
Until my charge is full,
あと少し夢見てたいな
I want to dream just a little more.
胸の中 ウサギとカメが
Inside my heart, the tortoise and the hare...
ずっと競争している
...are racing forever.
ドンと来いだよ
Bring it on!
ハンデありのノンフィクション
A non-fiction with a handicap.
いま いま この瞬間が
Now, now, this very moment...
スタート切るチャンスなんだ
...is the chance to start.
ドンと来いだよ
Bring it on!
気合入れてこんぷくしよう
Let's get fired up and 'Kon-puku'!
ほら ほら もうあっというま
Look, look, it's already over in a flash.
大逆転しちゃうもんね
I'm gonna make a huge comeback!
飛べ 飛べ もうちょい高く
Fly, fly, a little higher!
行け 行け もうちょい遠く
Go, go, a little further!
君と私 本気出せれば
If you and I get serious,
限界なんてちょちょいのちょいと
limits are no problem at all!
飛ばせ1000%
Let's fly at 1000%!
お弁当 海の玉手箱〜
A lunch box, a treasure chest from the sea...
それなら宝石箱や〜
Well then, it's a jewelry box!
どんぶらこ デザート流れて来い
Tumbling down, let the dessert float this way.
桃でもケーキでもいいの
Whether it's peaches or cake, it's fine.
食べすぎて まぶたが落ちてく
I ate too much, my eyelids are falling.
相撲で勝負だスイマ
Let's have a sumo match, sleepiness.
目が覚めてティーチャーが微笑んだ
I woke up and the teacher was smiling.
いのっ・こりっ・ね
Stay behind after class, okay?
世界中 巻き込みながら
While involving the whole world,
好きなだけ遊びたいな
I want to play as much as I like.
楽しいが一番！
Fun is number one!
100年後 100万年後には
100 years later, 1,000,000 years later...
昔ばなしに乗っけてよ
...put us in a fairy tale.
ドン詰まりこぽ
Stuck in a dead end, 'kopo'.
無敵になるモチベーション
Motivation to become invincible.
来た来た来た この感覚が
It's here, it's here, this feeling...
また頑張れる合図なんだ
...is the sign that I can keep going.
ドン詰まりこぽ
Stuck in a dead end, 'kopo'.
笑顔見せて行くぞのぞの
Let's go with a smile...
笑顔見せてなんのその
No matter what, show your smile
まだまだあれこんなもん
There's still more, this is nothing
大成功しちゃうもんね
We're going to be a huge success
飛べ 飛べ もうちょっとで届く
Fly, fly, we'll reach it in just a bit
行け 行け もうちょっとで変わる
Go, go, it'll change in just a bit
君と私
You and I
一緒だったら
If we're together
心配なんてなくなっちゃうと
Worries will disappear
小さいこと気にしません
I won't sweat the small stuff
質問！
Question!
あなたが鬼退治を任されたらどう戦いますか？
If you were tasked with oni slaying, how would you fight?
りゃー！ そりゃー！
Ryaa! Soryaa!
はい！ 鬼ヶ島に遊園地と温泉とサウナを作って
Yes! I'll build an amusement park, a hot spring, and a sauna on Onigashima...
毒気を抜いて平和的解決を図ります！
...to drain their malice and seek a peaceful resolution!
でもね たまに赤点取る日もあるよ
But you know, there are days when we fail too
そう うちら人間なんだもん
That's right, because we're only human
さあ お団子食べに行きますか
Come on, shall we go eat some dango?
諦めるなんて言葉
The word "giving up"...
絶対にないよ
...is definitely not in our vocabulary
ドンと来いだよ
Bring it on
ハンデ有りのノンフィクション
Non-fiction with a handicap
いま いま この瞬間が
Now, now, this very moment
スタート切るチャンスなんだ
Is the chance to make a start
ドンと来いだよ
Bring it on
気合い入れてこんちくしょう
Let's fire ourselves up, damn it
ほら ほら もうあっというま
Look, look, in the blink of an eye
大逆転しちゃうもんね
We're going to turn things around
飛べ 飛べ もうちょいだけ高く
Fly, fly, just a little bit higher
行け 行け もうちょいだけ遠く
Go, go, just a little bit further
君と私
You and I
本気出せば
If we give it our all
限界なんてちょいちょいちょいね
Limits are easy to overcome
フレフレ！ 私たちへ
Go, go! To us
フレフレ！ みんなへ
Go, go! To everyone
フレフレ！ インフレだって強く生きましょ
Go, go! Let's live strong even through inflation
フレフレ！ 私たちへ
Go, go! To us
フレフレ！ みんなへ
Go, go! To everyone
...と思えちゃうのは ちょっと反則じゃん
...to think that is a bit like cheating.
君の「可愛い」
Your "Cuteness"
知ってみてと言葉だけで
With just the words "Check it out,"
最大級の声も吹っ飛んじゃうくらい
To the point where even the loudest voice is blown away.
気にするのは君のことだけでいいんだよね
It's okay if I only care about you, right?
可愛いって言葉だけで
With just the word "cute,"
ここまで全部が正解なんだって
everything so far is the correct answer.
思えちゃうのは ちょっと反則じゃん
To think that is a bit like cheating.
最大級の 最大級の
Maximum, maximum,
maximum, maximum!
恋なんです、だって君の顔がこう言ってる
It's love, because your face is saying so.
最大級の 最大級の
Maximum, maximum,
maximum, maximum!
きゃるるんしてみて
Try to be "kyururun."
ね？
Right?
ヒトリゴトだよ
It's just a monologue.
恥ずかしいこと聞かないでよね
Don't ask me anything embarrassing.
キミノコトだよ
It's about you.
でもその先は言わないけどね
But I won't say any more than that.
ヒトリゴト 作詞：ケリー 作曲：谷口尚久 編曲：睦月周平
Hitorigoto | Lyrics: Kelly | Composition: Takahisa Taniguchi | Arrangement: Syuhei Mutsuki
掛け違えてる
Being misaligned,
ボタンみたいなもどかしさを
like buttons on a shirt, it's frustrating.
ほどけないまま
Still unable to untangle,
また難しくしようとしてる
I'm trying to make it complicated again.
伝えたい気持ちは今日も
The feelings I want to convey today, too,
言葉になる直前に
right before they turn into words,
変換ミスの連続で
due to a series of conversion errors,
ため息と一緒に飲み込んだら
when I swallow them along with a sigh,
ほろ苦い...
it's bittersweet...
ふとした時に探しているよ
I find myself looking for it,
君の笑顔を探しているよ
I'm looking for your smile.
無意識の中その理由は
Unconsciously, the reason for that,
まだ言えないけど
I still can't say.
一人でいると会いたくなるよ
I want to see you when I'm alone.
誰といたって会いたくなるよ
I want to see you no matter who I'm with.
たった一言 ねぇどうして
Just one word, hey, why
Ah 言えない
Ah, can't I say it?
その言葉 言えない
Those words, I can't say them,
この気持ち Ah 早く
these feelings, Ah, quickly,
気づいてほしいのに
even though I want you to notice.
1000ピースある
With a thousand pieces,
パズルみたいな選択肢と
like choices in a puzzle,
想像力が
and my imagination
判断力の邪魔をしちゃう
gets in the way of my judgment.
つかめない気持ちは今日も
My elusive feelings today, too,
可愛くない顔見せて
show an un-cute face,
自己嫌悪+後悔で
with self-loathing + regret,
ため込んだ「ごめんね」を吐き出すには
to spit out the stored-up "I'm sorry,"
ほど遠い...
it's far from it...
耳をすませば聞こえてくるよ
If I listen closely, I can hear it,
君の声だけ聞こえてくるよ
I can hear only your voice.
雑踏の中 気づかない
In the middle of the crowd,
ふりしているけど
I'm pretending not to notice.
隣にいると嬉しくなるよ
I'm happy when I'm next to you.
遠くにいると寂しくなるよ
I'm lonely when you're far away.
単純なこと でもどうして
A simple thing, but why
Ah 言えない
Ah, can't I say it?
その言葉 言えない
Those words, I can't say them,
この気持ち Ah もっと
these feelings, Ah, more,
素直になりたい
I want to be more honest.
泣き出しそうな空模様
The sky looks like it's about to cry,
頬に一粒
a single drop on my cheek,
雨かな...
is it rain...?
不安定な心 傘で隠した
I hid my unstable heart with an umbrella,
ヒトリゴトに全部隠した
I hid it all in my monologue.
君のこと ほんとはずっと
About you, honestly, always,
Ah...
ふとした時に探しているよ
I find myself looking for it,
君の笑顔を探しているよ
I'm looking for your smile.
無意識の中その理由は
Unconsciously, the reason for that,
まだ言えないけど
I still can't say.
一人でいると会いたくなるよ
I want to see you when I'm alone.
誰といたって会いたくなるよ
I want to see you no matter who I'm with.
たった一言 ねぇどうして
Just one word, hey, why
Ah 言えない
Ah, can't I say it?
その言葉 言えない
Those words, I can't say them,
この気持ち Ah 早く
these feelings, Ah, quickly,
気づいてほしいのに
even though I want you to notice.
さあみんな、はじまるよー！
Come on everyone, it's starting!
ワン、ツー、スリー、はい！
One, two, three, go!
それ！それ！それ！それ！
Sore! Sore! Sore! Sore!
マンマンマンマンマンマンマンマン... (はー どっこいしょー！)
Man-man-man-man... (Ha, dokkoisho!)
息が苦しい
I can't breathe...
すっからかんかん からっとけらっと
Completely empty, crisp and clear
マンマンマンマンマンマンマンマン... (はー どっこいしょー！)
Man-man-man-man... (Ha, dokkoisho!)
んんん、んん、あれ？音が出なーい！
Hmmm, hmm, huh? There's no sound!
うれしくって はしゃいじゃって どっどーんどーん
So happy and frolicking, boom-boom-boom
ゆーらゆらっと ひーらひらっと 花舞う彼方
Swaying, fluttering, beyond the dancing flowers
髪を結って 帯を巻いて ギュッギュッギュッ
Tie your hair, wrap your sash, tight-tight-tight
まだだまーだ やぐらは 始まったばかり！
The scaffold tower is just getting started!
もう一回！
One more time!
まーだだよ！
Not yet!
もう一回！
One more time!
モーイーヨー！
It's already enough!
届け届け 想いよ届け
Reach out, reach out, let these feelings reach you
追えば逃げて ぐるぐる回る
If you chase it, it runs away, spinning round and round
めっざすはいただき めっざすはぶちぎり
Aim for the top, aim for a runaway victory
おーそーるーることなかーれー
Have no fear!
んなこと言って どどどど どーすんの？ どーすんの？
Saying that, what what what what are you gonna do?
レッツゴー！
Let's go!
めっちゃくちゃ めっちゃくちゃ よーいそよいそ よーいそよいそ
Messy, messy, yoisho yoisho yoisho yoisho
おーどりおーどりくるえー！！
Dance, dance like crazy!!
めっちゃくちゃ めっちゃくちゃ よーいそよいそ よーいそよいそ
Messy, messy, yoisho yoisho yoisho yoisho
トレセン音頭で よーよいのよい！
With the Tresen Ondo, yoi-yoi-no-yoi!
めっちゃめちゃ めっちゃめちゃ あーいあいさー あーいあいさー
Very, very, aye-aye sir, aye-aye sir
おーどりおーどりくるえー！！
Dance, dance like crazy!!
めっちゃめちゃ めっちゃめちゃ あーいあいさー あーいあいさー
Very, very, aye-aye sir, aye-aye sir
トレセン音頭で よーよいの よーよいの よーよいのよい！
With the Tresen Ondo, yoi-yoi-no, yoi-yoi-no, yoi-yoi-no-yoi!
歌いすぎて 息が苦しい...
I sang too much, I can't breathe...
酸素だ、酸素だ、酸素を持ってこい！！
Oxygen, oxygen, bring me some oxygen!!
マンマンマンマンマンマンマンマン... (はー どっこいしょー！)
Man-man-man-man... (Ha, dokkoisho!)
(明日だ 明日だ！)
(It's tomorrow, it's tomorrow!)
(おーっぽんぴん！！)
(O-ppinpin!!)
止まらない... 止まらへん！
It doesn't stop... I can't stop it!
ゾーリをむりっと やーる気でてきた そう！！
Slip on the sandals, I'm feeling motivated, yeah!!
はー どっこいしょー！
Ha, dokkoisho!
んんん、んん、あれ？だれもやってなーい！
Hmm, hmm, huh? No one is doing it!
はあ...
Sigh...
こよい星がまたた...
Tonight the stars are twinkl...
...って言ってる場合かーい！！
...is no time for that!!
どどどど どーすんの？ どーすんの？ どどどど どーすんの？
What what what what are you gonna do? What what what what are you gonna do?
レッツゴー！！
Let's go!!
めっちゃくちゃ めっちゃくちゃ よーいそよいそ よーいそよいそ
Messy, messy, yoisho yoisho yoisho yoisho
おーどりおーどりくるえー！！
Dance, dance like crazy!!
めっちゃくちゃ めっちゃくちゃ よーいそよいそ よーいそよいそ
Messy, messy, yoisho yoisho yoisho yoisho
トレセン音頭で よーよいのよい！
With the Tresen Ondo, yoi-yoi-no-yoi!
めっちゃめちゃ めっちゃめちゃ あーいあいさー あーいあいさー
Very, very, aye-aye sir, aye-aye sir
おーどりおーどりくるえー！！
Dance, dance like crazy!!
めっちゃめちゃ めっちゃめちゃ あーいあいさー あーいあいさー
Very, very, aye-aye sir, aye-aye sir
トレセン音頭で よーよいの よーよいの よーよいの よーよいのよい！
With the Tresen Ondo, yoi-yoi-no, yoi-yoi-no, yoi-yoi-no, yoi-yoi-no-yoi!
はるかかなたの銀河から 君に届けスペースオペラ！
From a galaxy far away, reaching out to you, Space Opera!
ガラフタで作ったスペースシップ
A spaceship made of scrap metal
あふれそうなハートごと乗せて
Carrying our overflowing hearts
君のシグナル探索中
Searching for your signal
いまだこの星を飛ぶのだ
Now is the time to fly from this planet
チェック チェック 信号異常？
Check, check, signal anomaly?
行けば進路になるから大丈夫
If we go, it'll become our path, so it's okay
さあ ジャック ジャック 電波ジャックだ
Now, jack, jack, a radio jack
アンテナ 君の受信アップデート
Updating your antenna's reception
やっと出会えたね
We finally met
どこにいても見つけるよ
I'll find you no matter where you are
触れた気持ちを 歌に乗せて
Putting the feelings I touched into song
この宇宙すべてに ワンダホー！
To this whole universe, wonderful!
オペラ！スペースオペラ！ 君に届けアリア
Opera! Space Opera! Reaching out to you, an aria
想いが
My feelings...
舞い上がり
Soaring...
そう大好きって伝えきれない
Yes, 'I love you' is not enough to say it all
オペラ！それでもいいや その笑顔も涙も
Opera! Even so, it's fine, that smile and those tears too
不器用な愛情も
And this clumsy affection too
全部乗せて
Carrying it all
小さな星から見れば悲劇も 宇宙から見れば喜劇だ
From a small star it's a tragedy, from the universe it's a comedy
はるかかなたで恋をして 君に届けスペースオペラ！
Falling in love in the far distance, reaching out to you, Space Opera!
重なる周波数 つなぐ電波
Overlapping frequencies, connecting radio waves
聴かせて 君のカデンツァ
Let me hear your cadenza
描く点と点が夜空で逢って
Shining points meeting in the night sky
風船風描く星座
Constellations drawn by balloon wind
ずっと探してた また歌が生まれる意味を
Searching for the meaning of why songs are born again
気持ちなんて分かってもいないまま歌う
Singing without even understanding the feelings
それが遠く届き響き合ったとき この歌に 君が意味を...
When that reaches far and resonates, you gave meaning to this song...
…与えたんだ
...gave to me
1、2、12、ワンダフル!
One, two, one-two, wonderful!
オペラ! スペースオペラ! これはドラマじゃなくて
Opera! Space Opera! This isn't just a drama
君と僕は この宇宙でいま生きてる!
You and I are living in this universe right now!
オペラ! そんな奇跡に
Opera! For such a miracle
この喜劇も悲劇も 君と会えた感動も
This comedy, tragedy, and the emotion of meeting you
全部乗せたい!
I want to include it all!
さあ ラタタタタタタタラッタ
Come on, la-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-rat-ta
歌える トゥルットゥットゥットゥットゥルッ
I can sing, tu-ru-tu-tu-tu-tu-tu-ru
ちいさな星からみれば悲劇も
Even a tragedy when seen from a tiny star
宇宙からみれば喜劇だ
Is a comedy when seen from space
ラタタタタタタタラッタ
La-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-rat-ta
歌える トゥルットゥットゥットゥットゥルッ
I can sing, tu-ru-tu-tu-tu-tu-tu-ru
はるか彼方の銀河ごと君と歌え スペースオペラ
Sing with the galaxy far, far away, space opera
君とつくる スペースオペラ
The space opera I create with you
私いま最上級に可愛いの！
Right now, I'm at my peak cuteness!
君に振られて最上級に可愛いの！
After you dumped me, I'm at my peak cuteness!
これが乙女の逆襲だ
This is a girl's counterattack
最上級に可愛いの！
At my peak cuteness!
もう気づいてるかもしれないけど
You might have already noticed, but
言うわ 私ね
I'll say it: I'm
今とっても可愛い！
Very cute right now!
君が始めた恋 君が終わらすなんて
The love you started, for you to end it...
なんだそれ 泣いちゃうぞ 可愛い
What's with that? I'm gonna cry. Cute!
可愛い
Cute!
私どれだけ連絡待って
Just how much I waited for messages
通知をオンにしてたかなんて
And kept my notifications on
友達から聞いたよ
I heard it from a friend
連絡しすぎたって
Saying I messaged you too much
君が不安にさせるからじゃん
It's because you made me anxious
もう気にしてないけど
I don't care anymore, but
だって今
Because right now
君に振られて最上級に可愛いの！
After you dumped me, I'm at my peak cuteness!
自分史上1番
Number one in my history
ときめき放つわ
I'm radiating excitement
最上級に可愛いの！
At my peak cuteness!
認めなよ
Admit it
これが乙女の逆襲だ
This is a girl's counterattack
さすがに失恋直後は
As expected, right after the breakup
涙でぐちゃぐちゃで可愛くない
I was a mess from tears and not cute
君が泣かせたのに 雑なさよならだったな
You made me cry, and it was such a messy goodbye
なんだそれ 泣いちゃうぞ 可愛い
What's with that? I'm gonna cry. Cute!
可愛い
Cute!
二人しか知らないって
That you said only the two of us knew
言ってた話だって
Even those stories
どうしてあの子も知ってるの
Why does that girl know them too?
別れて良かったなんて
Things like "I'm glad we broke up"
思わせないで欲しかった
I didn't want to be made to feel that
好きだったから
Because I loved you
君に振られて最上級に可愛くなれました
After you dumped me, I became my peak cute self
むしろありがとう
Rather, thank you
最上級に可愛くなったって
For letting me become my peak cute self
ねぇ言って 知って
Hey, say it, know it
あいつがなんか可愛くなったって
That she somehow became cuter
ねぇ聞いて
Hey, listen
君に振られて最上級に可愛いの！
After you dumped me, I'm at my peak cuteness!
自分史上1番
Number one in my history
ときめき放つわ
I'm radiating excitement
最上級に可愛いの！
At my peak cuteness!
認めなよ
Admit it
これが乙女の逆襲だ
This is a girl's counterattack
最上級に可愛いの！
At my peak cuteness!
君に振られて最上級に可愛いの！
After you dumped me, I'm at my peak cuteness!
はい！ということで、ここまでお聞きいただきましたこの7曲！
Yes! So, those were the seven songs we've listened to so far!
みなさん、どうでしたか？
Everyone, how was it?
ありがとうございます！ありがとうございます！
Thank you! Thank you!
今回はちょっと初めてのデュエットが2曲ぐらいありまして
This time, we had about two duets for the first time
リアルエスケープと、わためぇと「独り言」
Real Escape with Watame and "Hitorigoto"
あずきちゃんのこの二人にね、初めてちょっと登場していただきました。
with AZKi-chan; I had these two appear for the first time.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
なんか二人にはね、ちょっとこの曲を歌ってほしいなー、一緒に歌いたいなーっていう曲を選ばせていただきました。
I chose songs that I really wanted them to sing, or songs I wanted to sing with them.
二つともね、好きな曲で...
Both are songs I love...
...な、なので、はい、一緒に歌って歌いたいわ～に合いそう！みたいな感じで選ばせていただいたのと...
...So, yes, I chose it thinking "I want to sing this together, it would suit the atmosphere!" and...
...先程お聞きいただいた「最上級に可愛いの」、
...the song you just heard, "Saijoukyuuni Kawaii,"
このね、おなじみの甘辛っぺでいいのかな？おなじみのメンバーでね...
with the familiar members of... Amakarappe, is that right?
この円形のこのステージで、ちょっと可愛いく歌わせていただきましたよ。どうでしたか？
I sang it cutely on this circular stage. How was it?
すごい快調！なんかブーンって、
It was great! Like "Vroom!"
みんながね、ブーンって上がってくるあの演出をさせていただきました。
that staging where everyone rose up like that.
可愛い。ありがとね、みんな歌ってくれてありがと。ありがとうございます。
So cute. Thanks, everyone, for singing along. Thank you so much.
ということでですね、こちらまだ嬉しいお知らせ残っております！はい！
And so, there's still some happy news left! Yes!
ここからはですね、告知をさせていただこうかなと思いますよ～！
From here, I'll be making some announcements!
えー、なんと、なんと、みんなちょっとお気づきなんじゃないかなと思いますけれども...
And, well, I think many of you might have already guessed...
今年も、えー、百鬼あやめ、えー、誕生日記念グッズ発売されます！やったー！
...this year too, Nakiri Ayame birthday commemorative goods will be released! Yay!
イェーイ！イェーイ！イェーイ！
Yay! Yay! Yay!
まだ最後まで、ちょっと最後まで見ててくださいね、ちょっと最後まで見ててね。
Please watch until the very end, okay? Stay tuned until the end.
はい。ということでですね、今回、こちらの、商品となっております！ドーン！
Yes. So, these are the products this time! Boom!
わー！めちゃくちゃ可愛い！今回も盛りだくさんとなっているんですけども...
Wow! So cute! There's a lot to go through this time too...
今回のイラストは、Tiv先生に書き下ろしさ、
The illustration this time was drawn
書き下ろししていただきました！ありがとうございます。めっちゃ可愛い、かわよ。ありがとうございます。
by Tiv-sensei! Thank you very much. It's so cute. Thank you.
じゃあね、ちょっと気になる詳細を見ていきましょう！まずは、こちら！
Now, let's look at the exciting details! First up is this!
ホログラムアクリルパネル！やったー！え、これめっちゃ可愛いでしょう？これ。キラキラしてるんです、これ、かわよ、可愛いね。
Hologram Acrylic Panel! Yay! Isn't this super cute? It's all sparkly. So cute.
えー、こちらですね、生誕祭のライブをちょっとね、テーマにした、テーマに合わせたパレードっぽい感じのアクリルパネルとなっております。
This one is an acrylic panel with a parade-like feel, themed after this birthday live.
かわよ。キラキラしてめっちゃ可愛いんね。はい。
So cute. The sparkle is really nice. Yes.
じゃあね、続きまして、こちら！ぬいぐるみキーホルダー！やったー！
Next up is this! Plushie Keychain! Yay!
え、ぬいぐるみのキーホルダーを、あ、グッズとして、よ、余のグッズとして出すの、たぶん初めてなんですけど...
It's probably the first time I'm releasing a plushie keychain as part of my merch...
ちょ、今回はね、あの、巫女衣装の、あの、小さい、このぐらいの、ぬいぐるみのキーホルダーを作らせていただきました。
This time, I made a small plushie keychain of this size, wearing my shrine maiden outfit.
このね、あの、ぜひ、あの、色んなとこつけて、あの、連れてってください。
Please attach it to various places and take it with you.
お出かけしやすいね、サイズ感となっておりますんでね、一緒に連れてってね。
It's a size that's easy to take out with you, so please bring it along.
はい。えー、続きまして、こちら！百鬼組ボディバッグとなっております！やったー！
Yes. Next is this! The Nakirigumi Body Bag! Yay!
ちょっとね、さりげなく、なんか、余、余、余推しですよってアピールできるような、デザインにさせていただきました。
I designed it so you can casually show that you're an Ayame fan.
ちょっとね、なんか、このバッグにお出かけキーホルダーやら何やらつけちゃって、一緒にお出かけ連れてってもらえたらな、嬉しいな、って感じですね。はい。
It would make me happy if you could attach the keychain or something to this bag and take it out with you. Yes.
ということでですね、続きまして、こちら！ぽよよ風フード付きタオル！
Moving on, next is this! Poyoyo-style Hooded Towel!
こちらね、イベントやら何やらでも、被って、百鬼組ですよってアピールできちゃう商品となっております。
This is an item you can wear at events or elsewhere to show you're part of the Nakirigumi.
みんなもね、ぽよよになれちゃいますよ、こうやって被ってね。真っ白になってください。
Everyone can become a Poyoyo by wearing this. Please turn pure white.
はい。なんかね、ぜひ、色んな、あの、グッズもね、ライブグッズとして、こう、色んな参戦グッズとして使えるかなというラインナップになっております。
Yes. The lineup is designed so that these items can be used as live goods or as gear for attending events.
え、続きましてですね、続いてはこちら！シチュエーションボイス！
Next, moving on, here's this! Situation Voice!
今回は、えー、ちょっと描き下ろしイラストに合わせた、遊園地をテーマにしたボイスとなっております。
This time, the voice track is themed around an amusement park, matching the newly drawn illustration.
一部ね、ちょっと紹介させていただいたグッズをちょっとストーリーにも、ちょっと出てくるので、そちらも楽しみに聞いていただければな、と思います。よろしくお願いします。
Some of the items I introduced will also appear in the story, so please look forward to that too. Thank you.
そして、フルセット購入特典もあります！こちら！
And there's also a full set purchase bonus! Here it is!
えー、数量限定版は、えー、直筆サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカードと、えー、誕生日ディナーデートのASMRボイスがついてきます。
The Limited Edition includes a cheki-style bromide card with a handwritten signature and a birthday dinner date ASMR voice.
ちょっと恥ずかしいですね。えー、このね、ブロマイド、カードも可愛いですね。
It's a bit embarrassing. And this bromide card is also cute.
えー、そしてですね、こちらが、なくなり次第、えー、箔押し複製サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカードと、えー、誕生日ディナーデートのASMRボイスとなっております。
And once those are gone, it will be a card with a foil-stamped signature and the ASMR voice track.
ね。あの、頑張って書くので、直筆をね、ぜひ皆さん、勝ち取ってください。よろしくお願いします。
I'll do my best to sign them, so everyone, please try to get a handwritten one. Thank you.
はい。えー、他にもですね、なんか、あの、今年の9月から発売された、あの、ホロライブオフィシャルカードゲームで使えるカードがですね、フルセット購入特典として1枚付いてくるみたいです！
Also, it seems a card for the Hololive Official Card Game will be included as a full set purchase bonus!
え、カードはですね、ホロライブプロダクションオフィシャルショップで購入された方のみの対象となっております。ぜひゲットしてくださいね。
The card is only for those who purchase from the official shop. Please be sure to get it.
改めてフルセットはこちらとなります！えー、誕生日記念フルセット、よろしくお願いいたします。
Once again, here is the full set! Birthday Commemorative Full Set, please check it out.
ねー、ちょっとぜひフルセットで買って、あの、ライブやら、色んなお出かけにやら連れて行ってくれたら余は嬉しいな、と思います。
I'd be really happy if you bought the full set and took the items to lives or on various outings with you.
はい、ということで以上、
Okay, and so, that's all for
余、百鬼あやめ誕生日記念2024のグッズ情報でした！
Nakiri Ayame's 2024 Birthday Memorial merchandise information!
みんな、よろしくお願いします！
Everyone, please check it out!
みんな、いろんなところに連れて行ってね！
Everyone, please take me to all sorts of places!
はい。ということで、今回...
Okay. And so, this time...
もう総勢15名のゲストに来ていただいて...
with a total of 15 guests coming...
こんなね、すごい素敵なステージで...
on such a wonderful stage as this...
いろんなギミックやらね、新しい挑戦を試み、
trying out various gimmicks and new challenges,
いろんなことをしながら、
while doing various things,
7回目の誕生日を迎えられて、
being able to celebrate my 7th birthday,
余は幸せです。本当にありがとうございます！
I am so happy. Thank you so much!
皆さん、たくさん見てくれてありがとうございました！
Thank you everyone for watching so much!
この後ですね、21時15分から、
After this, from 21:15,
人間様のアンコールライブが、ちょっと、ちょっとだけあるので、
the Ningen-sama Encore Live will be held for just a little bit,
よかったらそちらも見ていってくれたら嬉しいなと思います！
so I'd be happy if you could watch that too!
みんな、本当にありがとね！
Everyone, thank you so much!
アンコールライブでお会いしましょう！
Let's meet again at the Encore Live!
ED動画もあるから見てってね！
There's also an ending video, so check it out!
バイバイー！
Bye-bye!